<resources>
    <string-array name="task_desc">
        <item name="ballet">Express your graceful movements in the poem.</item>
        <item name="bikini">Embrace your body and feel confident going outside in a crazy look.</item>
        <item name="chilling">Take a moment to relax and unwind by doing yoga.</item>
        <item name="coffee">Savor a delicious cup of coffee outside your house.</item>
        <item name="dance">Let your favourite childhood song guide your dance moves.</item>
        <item name="dancing">Learn a dance from the video of your favourite artist.</item>
        <item name="doggie">Play and have fun with your friends.</item>
        <item name="dogjump">Go to the gym today with the joy and enthusiasm.</item>
        <item name="icecream">Indulge in your favorite ice cream flavor.</item>
        <item name="jumping">Jump on the trampoline in the toy shop.</item>
        <item name="laying">Lie down and watch the clouds passing by.</item>
        <item name="levitate">Go to the 3D room and experience new feelings.</item>
        <item name="loving">Show love and affection to someone dear either pet or friend.</item>
        <item name="meditating">Find inner peace through meditation and deep breathing.</item>
        <item name="messy">Embrace messiness and creativity and paint something crazy.</item>
        <item name="moshing">Let loose the trac of time and do something that excites you.</item>
        <item name="petting">Enjoy the act of getting to know people on the street.</item>
        <item name="plant">Buy and nurture a plant and witness its growth.</item>
        <item name="reading">Get lost in a captivating book.</item>
        <item name="readingside">What a movie from your bucket list.</item>
        <item name="rollerskating">Glide and have fun while roller skating.</item>
        <item name="rolling">Roll around and play as a child with your friends.</item>
        <item name="running">Feel the exhilaration of running in the morning on the sunrise.</item>
        <item name="selfie">Feed an animal on the street.</item>
        <item name="sitting">Try to slow down and feel how your body react on the rushing life.</item>
        <item name="sittingreading">Read a new genre for you in a bookshop.</item>
        <item name="sleek">Create a sleek and stylish outfit for today.</item>
        <item name="sprinting">Sprint with all your energy and help people who needs it.</item>
        <item name="strolling">Take a leisurely stroll and enjoy the surrounding nature.</item>
        <item name="swinging">Feel carefree while swinging on a swing.</item>
        <item name="unboxing">Buy yourself a present and unpack it with a wish.</item>
        <item name="zombieing">Play with children on your yard.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>